<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FiveAM.dev</title>
    <description>Horace is a simple Jekyll theme for writers and bloggers. Explore it yourself.</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:19:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bla bla This is just a demo - 2022-05-22</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Title&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bla bla bla&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Column A&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Column B&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Text A&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Text B&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-python highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kn&quot;&gt;from&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;collections&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kn&quot;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;namedtuple&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;Point&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;namedtuple&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;Point&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;x&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;y&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;])&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;point&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;Point&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;point&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/test-jupytext-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/test-jupytext-post</guid>
        
        <category>Python</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Advanced Markdown tips</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’ve gotten pretty comfortable with Markdown in Jekyll, then you may enjoy some more advanced tips about the types of things you can do with it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with the last post about the editor, you’ll want to be actually editing this post as you read it so that you can see all the Markdown code we’re using.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;special-formatting&quot;&gt;Special formatting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as bold and italics, you can also use some other special formatting in Markdown when the need arises, for example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;strike through&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;==highlight==&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;*escaped characters*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;writing-code-blocks&quot;&gt;Writing code blocks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two types of code elements which can be inserted in Markdown, the first is inline, and the other is block. Inline code is formatted by wrapping any word or words in back-ticks, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;like this&lt;/code&gt;. Larger snippets of code can be displayed across multiple lines using triple back ticks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;.my-link {
    text-decoration: underline;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get really fancy, you can even add syntax highlighting using &lt;a href=&quot;http://prismjs.com/&quot;&gt;Prism.js&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference-lists&quot;&gt;Reference lists&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The quick brown &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fox&quot; title=&quot;Wikipedia: Fox&quot;&gt;fox&lt;/a&gt;, jumped over the lazy &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dog&quot; title=&quot;Wikipedia: Dog&quot;&gt;dog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to insert links in markdown is using reference lists. You might want to use this style of linking to cite reference material in a Wikipedia-style. All of the links are listed at the end of the document, so you can maintain full separation between content and its source or reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;creating-footnotes&quot;&gt;Creating footnotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quick brown fox&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-noteref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; jumped over the lazy dog&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot; role=&quot;doc-noteref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Footnotes are a great way to add additional contextual details when appropriate. Ghost will automatically add footnote content to the very end of your post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;full-html&quot;&gt;Full HTML&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the best part of Markdown is that you’re never limited to just Markdown. You can write HTML directly in the Ghost editor and it will just work as HTML usually does. No limits! Here’s a standard YouTube embed code as an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cniqsc9QfDo?rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnote&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Foxes are red &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot; role=&quot;doc-backlink&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnote&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Dogs are usually not red &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot; role=&quot;doc-backlink&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/advanced-markdown-tips</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/advanced-markdown-tips</guid>
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Week With the Apple Watch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/strong&gt; is a smartwatch developed by Apple Inc. It incorporates fitness tracking and health-oriented capabilities as well as integration with iOS and other Apple products and services. The device is available in four variants: Apple Watch Sport, Apple Watch, Apple Watch Hermès, and Apple Watch Edition. The Watch is distinguished by different combinations of cases and first or third party interchangeable bands. Apple Watch relies on a wirelessly connected iPhone to perform many of its default functions such as calling and texting. It is compatible with the iPhone 5 or later models running iOS 8.2 or later, through the use of Bluetooth or Wi-Fi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Announced by Tim Cook on September 9, 2014, the device was available for pre-order on April 10 and began shipping on April 24, 2015. The Apple Watch quickly became the best-selling wearable device, with the shipment of 4.2 million smartwatches in the second quarter of 2015, according to analyst firm Canalys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“You can only do so many things great, and you should cast aside everything else.” ― Tim Cook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumors surrounded an Apple-developed wearable back as far as 2011, which conceptualized the device as a variation of the iPod that would curve around the user’s wrist, and feature Siri integration. On February 10, 2013, both The New York Times and The Wall Street Journal reported that Apple was beginning to develop an iOS-based smartwatch with a curved display. On February 12, 2013, Bloomberg reported that Apple’s smartwatch project was “beyond the experimentation phase in its development”, and had a team of at least 100 designers were working on the project. Further reports in March 2013 indicated that Apple planned to release the device by the end of the year. In July 2013, Financial Times reported that Apple had begun hiring more employees to work on the smartwatch, and that it was targeting a possible retail release in late 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;unveiling--release&quot;&gt;Unveiling &amp;amp; Release&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In April 2014, Apple CEO Tim Cook told The Wall Street Journal that the company was planning to launch new product categories that year, but did not reveal any specifics. In June 2014, Reuters reported that production was expected to begin in July for a release in October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Watch was first unveiled after a classic and ever infamous “We do have ‘one more thing’…” slide, which heard enormous applause, on September 9, 2014 during a press event which also saw the introduction of the iPhone 6. After the reveal video, the auditorium erupted with applause while Tim Cook rolled back his sleeve, revealing an Apple Watch on his wrist. Speaking about the device, Apple CEO Tim Cook explained that Apple Watch was “a new, intimate way to communicate from your wrist, and a comprehensive health and fitness device.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>/a-week-with-the-apple-watch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/a-week-with-the-apple-watch</guid>
        
        <category>Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
